Sameeksha Gudla

863-957-6515 • sameekshag145@gmail.com • linkedin.com/sameekshagudla

Profile Summary

Innovation and performance-driven individual with experience and strong understanding in Software Testing. Recognized for the ability to work and remain calm under pressure. Excellent team-work and multi-tasking with a collaborative attitude and can effectively communicate with a vision and zeal.

Skills and Certifications

- **Programming Languages:** C, OOPS, Python
- **Web Technologies:** HTML5
- Test Management Tools: Jira
- **Protocols:** RS 485
- Certified in **Data Science with Python** issued by Coursera
- Certified in C programming language(offline)
- Completed certification in SQL server.

Academic Qualifications

Degree	Year	Institute, University/ Board	— % /CGPA
B. Tech (CSE)	2022	Mallareddy Engineering College, Hyderabad	7.02
12 th (<i>BIE</i>)	2018	Sri Gayathri Junior College, Hyderabad	77.8%
10 th (CBSE)	2016	Bhadrachalam Public School, Sarapaka	6.4

Professional Experience

Work Experience:

OTIS Lead Design Center

Software Engineer

(August2022-December2022)

Hvderabad

Otis One Multimedia

- Part of system testing team.
- Understood and implemented as per SDLC process.
- Performed Embedded device side and cloud side testing.
- Validation of Displays from 7inch to 18inch on multiple Elevator controllers.
- Identified Blocker Bugs.
- In line with Agile process standards.
- Been a good Team Player.

ı		
ı		

Keypoint Technologies

Software Engineer

(Currently Working)

Hyderabad Xploree

- Part of Xploree team as a QA.
- Performing Mobile Testing.
- Verifying Xploree app and Keyboard related issues.
- Performing end to end testing.

Internships

VVV Infotech

Web Technology Intern

(June2018-July2018)

- Used HTML 5 version in detail.
- Developed Web Pages and Websites through HTML.

Video and Design Intern

(June 2021-July 2021)

- Used Adobe Premiere Pro for editing videos and reels.
- Used Canva tool for creating GIFS and stickers for Instagram stories.
- Built some ideas for improving 5 Instagram city pages.

Academic Project

Correlated matrix factorization for recommendation with implicit Feedback (CMF) |Python programming language|

- Programmed a search engine query where the machine uses matrix factorization to generate input output in the form of recommendations
- The system uses two approaches a) content-based filtering b) collaborative-filtering to make recommendations with proper feedback also displays the output in the form of pie charts.

Price based resource allocation for edge computing a market equilibrium |Cloud computing|

• The main contribution is to suggest the famous concept of General Equilibrium in Economics as an effective solution for underlying edge computing resource allocation problem.

Co-curricular

- Participated in Technical Fest.
- Organized and Coordinated for many events like Fests and Freshers Party.
- **Seminars:** Participated in a Guinness World Record 1day Event -Most users to take an online computer programming lesson.
- Workshops: Participated in Machine Learning Workshop conducted by kyrion technologies pvt ltd at IITH.

Extra- Curricular

- NCC- Passed with "A grade" as cadet in NCC: 2014-2015.
- **Sports** Participated in the state level Athletics meet.